(English Subtitle) Growing.Pains.S01E05 -= Superdad =- Subripped by zerox
-麦克! -救命
- Mike! - Help.
-麦克，把这疯狗带走 -救命
- Mike, get that rabid animal out of here. - Help.
爸爸，斯图不是疯狗 那叫活泼
Come on, Dad. Stuart's not rabid. He's peppy.
吃人的动物不能用“活泼”来形容
Mike, animals that live off human toes are not "peppy."
这下算了.
This is great.
我要帮帮不在家的邻居，做点好事.
I mean, I'm trying to do a good deed for a neighbor who's out of town...
你们抱怨什么？
and all you guys can do is complain.
你怎么只会对这样走路的人做好事
How come you only do good deeds for neighbors who walk like this?
你懂不懂“善有善报”这句话？
Ben, does the phrase "one good turn deserves another" mean anything to you?
麦克，你懂不懂.
Mike, does the phrase "get that dog out of here...
“把狗带走，否则格杀勿论”这句话？
"before I punt it through the greenhouse" mean anything to you?
嗨，凯罗
Hi, Carol.
嗨
Hi.
怎么了？
What's the matter, Carol?
我找不到花生酱
I cant find the peanut butter.
妈妈什么时候回家？
When's Mom coming home?
往常一样
Usual time.
可以打电话给她吗？
Can I call her at work?
若有急事，当然可以
Course you can, sweetheart. If it's important.
请问麦姬.西弗在吗？
Yeah, is Maggie Seaver there, please?
让她回来后打给凯罗，急事
Yeah, could you tell her to call Carol when she gets back? It's really important.
好的
Okay.
谢谢，再见
Thanks. Bye.
有话要对我说吗？
Something you want to talk to me about?
不知道.
I don't know.
我需要离开吗？
Want me to leave you alone?
不知道.
I don't know.
我需要扮小坏弹琴.
Do you want me to stick large ripe vegetables in my ear...
来逗逗你吗？
and play the accordion?
别这样，记得你小时候.
Hey, come on. Remember what we used to do when you we're just a little girl...
有困难时会怎样？
and you had a problem?
我会推你过来，哔哔 转过身.
I'd steer you over here, beep-beep, spin you around...
抱你上来
and up on the counter like that...
接着我们面对面谈
so that we could have a little face-to-face chat.
-是的 -现在行不通了
- Yeah. - Doesn't work anymore.
来，跟我谈谈
Come on, talk to me.
今天是德国小组出售玩具熊最后一天
Today was the last day of the German Club Gummy Bear sale and...
也是让凯文注意到我的最后机会
well, that was my last real chance to get Kevin to notice me...
明天就要举行舞会
before the dance tomorrow night.
凯文的朋友马克过来买玩具熊
And Kevin's friend Mark was coming up to get a Gummy...
玛丽莎说她听到马克说他说.
and Melissa said she heard Mark said he said--
等等，谁说的？
Wait, wait. Who said?
-凯文说的 -说什么？
- Kevin said. - Said what?
说.
Said....
说我像一只玩具熊
Said I look like a Gummy Bear.
亲爱的，他这话是善意的
Well, honey, I'm sure he meant it in a nice way.
算了吧，他认为我是一只胖熊
Come off it, Dad. I mean, the boy thinks I look like a bear.
是我坏陋
I'm just ugly.
你不像一只胖熊
You do not look like a bear.
但如果老是认为自己坏
But if you walk around thinking that you...
长大后就会变成这样，瞧
look ugly, then you're going to end up looking like this. Look.
看见自己了吗？
Can you see yourself?
如果认为自己漂亮.
Now if you walk around knowing you're pretty...
因为你确实漂亮
because you are...
那么心情就会好，长大后会变成这样
then you're gonna feel better. You're gonna look like this.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
重要的是凯文怎么看
I think it's more important what Kevin thinks.
好.
Okay...
你亲耳听到凯文说.
but did you actually hear Kevin say...
他觉得你像一只玩具熊吗？
that he thought you looked like a Gummy Bear?
没有，但玛丽莎说听见了
No, but Melissa said she heard he said it.
你相信玛丽莎的每一句话？
Well, since when did you believe everything Melissa says she heard?
她有时候确实让人怀疑
Well, she does make you wonder sometimes.
她还发誓说在JC百货看到明星了
I mean, she swore she saw Mick Jagger at JC Penney's last week.
那里的家具确实大减价
Well, they did have that big sale in Home Furnishings.
爸爸
Dad.
拜托，我认为.
Come on, I just think that...
你应该区分“听说凯文说的话”和.
you should take your cues about what Kevin thinks...
“凯文亲口说的话”
from what Kevin says himself.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
我要买溜冰鞋
I need new ice skates.
我听错了？
Did I miss something?
明晚大家都会去溜冰
Well, everybody's going to be at the skating rink tomorrow night...
我会靠近凯文，听听他会说什么
and I can skate by Kevin and see if he says anything to me.
我们明早去商店.
Tomorrow morning you and I go down to Macy's...
买一双新的溜冰鞋
and we buy you a brand-new pair of skates.
也许能在商店碰到明星呢
Who knows, maybe well even run into Tina Turner in Small Appliances.
爸爸，谢谢
Thanks, Dad.
凯罗
Carol.
-凯罗 -妈妈，我在这
- Carol. - I'm in here, Mom.
-上当了？ -是啊
- Fooled you, didn't l? - Yeah.
甜心
Hi, sweetheart.
凯罗呢？我收到留言说她找我
Wheres Carol? I got a message that she wanted to talk to me.
她去劳莉家了，你今天好吗？
She's over at Laurie's. How was your day?
又要临时改稿
Another last-minute rewrite.
平生首次打字这么快 手指现在还在跳呢
I've never typed so fast in my life. My fingers are still wiggling.
那就别浪费了
Don't be wasting those wiggling fingers.
来，帮我揉揉肩膀
Here, try them right here below the shoulder blade.
杰森
Oh, Jason.
很好，谢了
Perfect. Thank you.
凯罗要谈什么？ 吉姆说她很伤心
So what did Carol want to talk about? Jim said she sounded very upset.
她说凯文有可能认为.
Yes, well, it seems she has reason to believe that Kevin thought...
她长得像玩具熊
that she looked like a Gummy Bear.
凯文？德国小组的凯文？
Kevin? The one in the German Club?
是德国小组的组长
My dear, the chancellor of the German Club.
自从啤酒节派对以来.
Oh, no. She's had a crush on him since--
她一直暗恋他
Yes, since the Oktoberfest polka party.
可怜的孩子，她一定很伤心了
Poor kid. She must be miserable.
她回家后我会找她谈谈
Well, I'll talk to her when she gets home.
-她没事了 -是吗？
- She's fine now. - She is?
是的，我们谈过，谈妥了
Yeah, we talked it over. Figured it out.
-你？ -是的
- You did. - I did.
你这样说只是不想让我愧疚吧？
Honey, you don't have to say that just so I won't feel guilty.
不是的
I'm not, Maggie.
我和凯罗谈了个清清楚楚，明明白白
No, we talked the whole thing over through and through, inside and out.
哭了，笑了，拥抱了 最后还一起唱歌
We cried. We laughed. We hugged. We closed with a song.
杰森，那就太好了 不过我还是会找她谈
That's good, Jason. But if you don't mind, I think I'll talk to her just the same.
她没事了
She's fine, Maggie.
亲爱的，她嘴上说说而已
Honey, she always says she's fine.
她何时回来？
Now when's she coming home?
你认为我要单方面终止协议？
You don't think I can hold up my end of the bargain, do you?
什么协议？
Jason, what bargain?
“你工作..”
Come on, the bargain where you go back to work...
“我留在家照顾孩子”的协议
and I stay here and take care of the kids.
-杰森 -你认为.
- Oh, Jason. - No. You don't think...
我办不到？
that I can handle it, do you?
-杰森，不是我认为.. -尽管我恰好是.
- Jason, it's not that I don't think-- - No, no, no. Even though I happen to be...
-一位职业心理医生 -杰森.
- a highly skilled professional counselor... - Oh, Jason.
我曾成功劝阻一名跳鲨鱼池的人
... who once talked a man down from the rim of a shark tank.
我曾经在警察抓人前两周.
No, no. I mean, because I was the guy...
准确预测那名犯人.
who predicted two weeks before the police caught Son of Sam...
正是来自新罗谢尔的邮差.
that he would turn out to be an ugly mailman from New Rochelle...
因为他跟邻居的狗说话
who talked to his neighbors dog.
我认为你是一名出色的心理医生
Jason, it's not that I don't think that you're a wonderful psychiatrist.
但你不是一名母亲
But you're just not a mother.
那就好了，这围裙穿着真不舒服
Well, that's fine with me because this girdle is killing me.
本，爸妈呢？
Hey, Ben. Wheres Mom and Dad?
麦克，有何不可告人？
Hey, Mike. What you hiding from them?
我？隐瞒亲爱的妈妈..？
Me? Hide something from my beloved mother and--
不!又一只!
Oh, no. Not another one.
会咬人吗？
Will it bite me?
怎么了本？不认得老朋友斯图了？
What's the matter, Ben? Don't you recognize your old pal, Stuart?
-麦克，斯图是黑色的 -又怎样？
- Mike, Stuart is black. - So?
-这狗是白色的 -那怎样？
- This dog is white. - So?
这是明显的不同
So I think that's a noticeable difference.
你得帮我，斯图跑掉了
Look, Ben. You gotta help me. Stuart ran away.
-温蒂定会宰了你 -除非她不知道
- Wendy's going to kill you. - Not if she doesn't find out.
麦克，即使是你的女朋友.
Mike, even one of your girlfriends...
也有可能记得自己狗的颜色
has a shot at remembering the color of her own dog.
我会应付温蒂的
I'll take care of Wendy.
你确保爸妈不知道就行了
You just make sure Mom and Dad don't find out.
大家好
Hi, guys.
什么狗？
What dog?
-谁说狗了？ -我没有
- Who said anything about a dog? - Not me.
-妈妈 -甜心
- Hi, Mom. - Hi, sweetheart.
你好吗？
How are you?
很好，时间刚刚好
Fine. Great, just in time for my show.
我收到留言了 要不是整天不在办公室.
I got your message, and I would've called you back...
我早就回你电话了
but I was out of the office all day.
妈妈，没关系
That's okay, Mom.
瞧那家伙
Look at this guy.
什么节目？
What is this?
The Sturgeons of Pitt Street.
管家干嘛趴在地上？
Why is the butler on all fours?
家里的狗死了，他们不敢告诉婆婆
The family dog died, and they didn't have the heart to tell Grandma.
你要谈谈今天在学校的事吗？
So, honey, you wanna talk about what happened at school today?
-凯罗？ -你刚说什么？
- Carol? - Mom, what'd you say?
凯文的话一定让你很伤心了
You must be really upset about what Kevin said.
广告来了，好
Good. A commercial.
咱聊聊
So lets talk.
这个凯文是怎么了？
What's with this Kevin anyway?
我已经跟爸爸谈过了
I already talked the whole thing through with Dad.
也许女人之间的谈话.
I know that, but I thought maybe a woman-to-woman talk....
不必了，妈妈，我没事
No, really, Mom. I'm fine.
真的？
You are? You're sure?
亲爱的，你不用害怕让我有愧疚感
Honey, you don't have to say that just so that I won't feel guilty.
我发誓我没事
No, I swear it's okay, Mom. You know...
还以为你回去工作我会不习来惯.
I thought I wasn't gonna like it when you went back to work...
现在爸爸在家也挺好的
but it's really kind of neat having Dad at home now.
很好
That's great.
那个鲟鱼节目开始没有？
Hey, those wacky Sturgeons on yet?
-爸爸，过来坐中间 -好的
- Come on, Dad. Sit in the middle. - Yeah. Okay.
-妈妈，过去一点 -好的
- Could you move over a little, Mom? - Yeah.
很好看的
You're gonna love this.
嗨，我是温蒂
Hi, it's Wendy.
温蒂，进来
Hi, Wendy. Come on in.
-还好吗？ -很好
- How you doing? - Fine.
假期怎样？
How was your vacation?
很棒，我们首先去了欧洲 接着去了法国
It was great. First we went to Europe, and then we went to France.
你们的旅行社真棒
Yes, well, you must have quite a travel agent.
麦克，温蒂来了
Mike, Wendy's here.
斯图没带给你们许多麻烦吧？
I hope Stuart wasn't too much trouble for you.
斯图？没有
Stuart? No, no.
自从喂它吃邻居的孩子后.
No, no, once we started feeding him the neighbors children...
它好像人间蒸发了
we hardly knew he was here.
-温蒂 -麦克
- Hey, Wendy. - Hi, Mike.
嗨，小斯图
Hi, Stuey-pooey.
温蒂，看它见到你后多高兴!
Wow, just look how glad he is to see you, Wendy.
真像斯图!
That does look like Stuart, doesn't it?
连颜色也一样
Same color and everything.
温蒂，带斯图回家吧
Yes. Wendy, why don't I take you and Stuart home?
斯图，来吧，对了，好狗狗
Come on, Stuart. Come on. Yeah, that's it, good dog. Yeah.
温蒂，瞧它.
Just look at him, Wendy. I mean...
知道你要回来，它太兴奋了.
he was so excited about you coming home last night...
昨晚彻夜不眠，现在已经精疲力尽
that he didn't sleep a wink. And now, of course, he's exhausted.
-本 -爸爸？
- Ben? - Yeah, Dad?
麦克对斯图怎样了？
What did Mike do to Stuart?
-要说真相？ -是的
- The truth, Dad? - Yeah, Ben.
麦克没对斯图怎么样，再见
Mike didn't do anything to Stuart. Bye, Dad.
-嗨，甜心 -嗨
- Hi, sweetheart. - Hello.
-凯罗呢？ -不知道
- Where's Carol? - I don't know.
我们要去度假？
Are we going on vacation here?
不，我要带凯罗到城里玩
No, no, I just thought I'd take Carol into the city for the day.
看看画展.
You know, take in a couple of art galleries...
接着去绿色餐馆吃饭
run up to Tavern on the Green for lunch...
或者逛逛布朗克斯动物园
and then maybe pop over to the Bronx Zoo.
凯罗一定爱看从底特律运来的白色猎狗
I know Carols been dying to see that albino hyena on loan from Detroit.
底特律有这些东西？
Those things come from Detroit?
如果有时间的话.
Anyway, I thought if we had time--
你告诉凯罗了吗？
Listen, sweetheart, does Carol know about all this?
没有，怎么了？
No, why?
我今天约了凯罗逛商店.
Well, Carol and I we're planning to go shopping together today...
要买溜冰鞋
for a new pair of skates.
这对她来说很重要
I think it's important to her...
因为凯文和其它人.
because, well, you know, Kevin and the other kids...
今天下午要去溜冰
are all going skating this afternoon.
舞会就在今晚举行
Yes, and you know the big dance is tonight.
-不是吧？ -是的
- No. - Oh, yes.
我不知道呢
No, I didn't realize that.
那就归你管了
But then that's more your area now.
亲爱的，你俩玩得开心点
Well, honey, you two have a good time.
-麦姬，要一起去吗？ -不了，我只会妨碍你们
- Maggie, you want to come with us? - No, I'd just be in the way.
别傻了
No, no. Don't be ridiculous.
我在家也很好玩
No, no, I can have fun here. Really.
洗洗衣服，清洁厕所
I'll just do the laundry, maybe clean a few toilets.
你不介意我和凯罗一起吧？
Does it bother you that Carol and I have plans together?
不介意
No. No.
这是好事
I think it's great.
她昨晚没空跟我聊
I mean, sure, she didn't have time to talk to me last night...
今天没空陪我
and she doesn't have time to be with me today...
我很高兴你俩在一起
but I love seeing the two of you together.
你是她爸爸，她是你女儿
You're her father. She's your daughter.
你们是父女，父女应该融洽
You're father and daughter. You should do things together.
做些父女做的事情，我替你们高兴
Father and daughter things. I'm very happy for you.
-麦姬 -怎么了？
- Maggie. - What?
凯罗那天气冲冲放学回来.
You know, when Carol came home from school yesterday all upset...
她真的要找你
she really wanted to talk to you.
是的，她死也不肯跟爸爸聊
Oh, yes. it was like pulling teeth to get her to open up to old Dad.
是吗？
Yeah?
她还是需要妈妈的
She still needs her mother, you know.
有时候我感觉不到这点
Sometimes I don't feel like it.
她确实需要你
She does.
家里穿围裙的还是你
And you still wear the girdle in the family.
-是吗？ -而且穿得很漂亮
- Yeah? - And very nicely.
你是说我有点过火了？
So you're saying that I'm overreacting a bit.
不，我是说你太过火了
No, no, I'm saying you're overreacting a lot.
爸爸，这是斯图成长的一个阶段
Dad, I'm telling you it's just a phase that Stuart's going through.
人会改变，狗也一样
I mean, people change, dogs change.
你没读过吗？
Look, did you ever read Passages?
温蒂，怎么了？
Wendy. ?Que pasa? How's it going?
小斯图，怎样了？
Hey, Stuart. How you doing, little fella?
麦克，这不是斯图
Mike, this isn't Stuart.
温蒂，温蒂.
Wendy. Wendy. Wendy.
不是斯图是谁？
Who would this be if it's not Stuart?
不知道，这狗湿了会掉色
I don't know, Mike. But this dog changes colors when he gets wet.
斯图不会这样的
Stuart would never do that.
报纸上有篇文章.
You know, theres an article about this in the paper.
说宠物偶尔会改变颜色
They're saying pets are changing colors left and right now.
那是因为酸雨的关系
It's that acid rain, you know.
麦克，瞧瞧
Mike, look.
在辛辛那提有一只髯狗变紫色了
There's a schnauzer in Cincinnati that turned purple.
听说这是完全正常的
They say it's perfectly normal.
报纸还在楼上，我去拿
I have the article upstairs. I'll go get it.
麦克，别动
Mike, stop.
坐下
Sit.
你对斯图怎样了？
Now what did you do to Stuart?
让它跑掉了
I lost him.
我到处找也找不到
Look, I looked everywhere, but I couldn't find him.
温蒂，原本我要告诉你的
Wendy, I would've told you the truth but...
但是我扪心自问.
then I asked myself:
真相是什么？
What is truth?
是诚实吗？
Is it honesty?
还是苦楚？
Or is it pain and grieving?
还是姑娘美丽的笑靥？
Or is it the smile on a beautiful girls face?
你知道我的答案了吧
I guess you know what I think the truth is.
你弄来一条白狗，染成黑色
Now you took a white dog and you dyed him black.
谁要是把一条黑狗托付给我麦克.
Hey, when somebody leaves a black dog with Mike Seaver...
谁就能要回一条黑狗!
they get a black dog back.
温蒂，真是对不起
Look, Wendy, I'm really sorry about all of this.
你肯定很喜爱斯图了
I know how much you must have loved Stuart.
-什么？谁喜爱斯图了？ -什么？
- Are you kidding? Who could love Stuart? - What?
我们全家度假就是为了躲开斯图
My family went on vacation to get away from Stuart.
什么？
They what?
但是我喜欢这条狗，很温驯
But I love this dog. He's so sweet.
我叫它小麦克好了
I think I'll name him Mikey.
不，叫它小小麦克
No, make that Mikey-Poo.
爸爸，听到了吧？ 她要叫它小小麦克
Did you hear that, Dad? She's gonna name it Mikey-Poo.
今晚见
I'll see you tonight.
-再见 -好的，再见
- Bye. - Yeah, okay. Bye.
爸爸，我知道教训了 我以后不敢了
Well, I learned my lesson, Dad. I'll never do that again.
当然了
No, you wont, Mike.
因为我要关你一辈子
Because you're grounded for the rest of your life.
-爸爸，你..一辈子？ -再加一个月
- Dad, you.... Life? - And a month after that.
麦克怎样了？
What's with Mike?
-我要关他一辈子 -又来了？
- I just grounded him for life. - Again?
真是不敢相信
I do not believe it.
亲爱的，怎么了？
Honey, what's wrong?
爸爸，你猜玛丽莎说的话
Dad, you're not gonna believe what Melissa told me.
什么？
What?
玛丽莎说马克告诉凯文.
Melissa told me that Mark told Kevin...
我经常流汗
that I sweat a lot.
宝贝，我们昨天不是说好了.
Well, sweetheart, didn't we decide yesterday...
玛丽莎的话不大可信吗？
that Melissa's really not that reliable a source?
爸爸，现在一切都不同了
Yeah, but, I mean, everything's different now, Dad.
事情一发不可收拾
I mean, the whole thing is blown wide open.
玛丽莎说.
You see, Melissa said that she--
等等，还是让专家来处理吧
Hey, wait. You know, this would be a good one to run by the old pro here.
好
Okay.
接着我跟马克聊 他说他从没有那样说
But then I talked to Mark, and he said he never even said that...
玩具熊的事也一样
or the Gummy Bear thing, either.
马克，哪个马克？
Mark. Who's Mark?
接着凯西说她当时在场.
But then Cathy tells me that she was right there...
听到马克告诉凯文我经常流汗
when Mark told Kevin that I do sweat a lot.
能告诉我马克是谁吗？ 还有昨天的事.
Honey, if you could just tell me who Mark is and what happened yesterday--
妈妈，这兴昨天无关
Mom, this has nothing to do with how it happened yesterday.
问题是不知道玛丽莎和马克 哪个可信
The point is I don't know whether I trust Melissa or Mark...
-因为凯西说.. -等等，宝贝
- cause Cathy says-- - Wait, wait, wait, sweetheart.
你说过凯西也喜欢凯文
Now you said that Cathy also had a thing for Kevin.
对，那？
Yeah, so?
那就是说凯西也不可信
Well, that doesn't make Cathy a very reliable source, either.
天哪，这就是说大家都有问题
Oh, God, Dad. You know what this means? This means everybody's in on it.
-麦姬，等等 -太不公平了
- Maggie, wait. - Dad, it's just not fair.
亲爱的，若是凯文值得你喜欢.
Honey, look, if Kevin is really worth caring for...
他自然会有自己的想法
then he's gonna make up his own mind.
他已经做出选择了
Yeah, well, I guess he already has...
他没有邀请我去舞会
"cause he didn't ask me to the dance.
麦姬，别生气 凯罗只是气在头上
Maggie, don't be mad. Carol's just upset.
-她没有要排挤你 -我没有生气
- She didn't mean to exclude you. - I am not mad.
我只是讨厌那些.
I am just tired of people taking things out of the cabinets...
不把东西放回柜子的人
and not putting them back where they belong.
-你要找什么？ -不知道
- Well, what are you looking for? - I don't know.
是不是那瓶1982年吃完的.
Well, on the off-chance that it's the mango chutney...
芒果酱？
we finished it in 1982.
麦姬，我理解你的心情
Come on, Maggie. I know what you're feeling.
你无法理解我的心情
You do not have any idea what I am feeling, Dr. Seaver.
听我说.
Hey, look--
你也许理解凯文 马克和玛丽莎的心情.
No, you may know what Kevin, Mark, and Melissa are feeling...
但你不理解我的心情
but you do not know what I am feeling.
麦姬，我没有要排挤你
Maggie, I tried to include you--
杰森，别客套了
Don't patronize me, Jason.
还说我是专家，嗟来之食
Throwing me a bone, calling me an old pro.
若干年后 或许在老人节才能让我回来
Maybe in a few years you can bring me back for Old-Timers Day.
我们不是谈过了吗？
We talked about all of this.
玩具熊事件暴发时.
I just happened to be the guy who was here...
我刚好在家而已
the day the whole Gummy Bear thing exploded in our faces.
不单是玩具熊，过去3个月以来
It's not just the Gummy Bears, Jason. It's the whole past three months.
你宠爱孩子的方式.
The way you've been pampering the children.
怎么了？
What?
制作本最爱的巧克力甜饼
Making Bens favorite chocolate chip cookies.
这有什么不对？
What's wrong with that?
“有什么不对”？
"What's wrong with that? "
不对的是你把我从孩子的生活中 排挤出去
What's wrong with that is you"re edging me out of my children's lives.
排挤出去？这就是你的想法？
Edging you out? Is that what you think?
你是专家，不如你说说我的想法
I don't know. You're the expert. Why don't you tell me what I think?
好的
Okay.
你因为回去工作而感到愧疚
I think you feel guilty about going back to work.
当然了
Of course I do.
你想要我多陪孩子们
And I think you want me to be here to spend time with the kids.
当然了
Of course I do.
你想要我善于照顾孩子
And I think you want me to be good at it.
当然了
Of course I do.
但这方面我不能超越你
But you don't want me to be as good as you are.
当..当然了
Of course I do.
那个.
Well...
也许不是
maybe I don't.
麦姬，在我上班时.
You know, Maggie, I was at work...
本踏出了他的第一步
when Ben took his first step...
凯罗说出了第一句话
and when Carol spoke her first sentence...
还有麦克.
and when Mike...
麦克第一次犯罪
committed his first illegal act.
这些我都错过了
I missed out on all that.
现在我有机会了.
And now I have the chance...
可以更靠近孩子们 花更多时间陪他们
to be closer to the kids, spend more time...
你不高兴？
and you begrudge that?
杰森，不是的，真的.
Oh, Jason, I don't. Really--
也许是的，我也曾有那种感觉
No, maybe you do. I know that feeling, too.
逝去的是时光
Because it's time that goes.
一去不复返
And it never comes back.
他们长大了.
They grow up...
叫人伤心
and it hurts.
是的
Yeah.
很伤心
It hurts.
回去工作感到愧疚吗？
Are you sorry you went back to work?
要回家吗？
You want to come home?
不要
No, I don't.
我猜.
I guess....
我是想拥有全部
I guess I just want to have it all.
这是不可能的
But you cant.
凯罗呢？
How's Carol?
她不用跟凯文去舞会
Well, she's not going to the dance with Kevin.
-太糟糕了 -是的
- Oh, no, that's too bad. - Yeah.
但还有另外一个刺激的约会
But she does have a chance at another date that she was pretty excited about.
-真的？约会谁？ -真的
- Really? Really? Who with? - Oh, yeah.
不大清楚，她说过是什么白色猎狗
I don't know exactly, but she said something about an albino hyena.
-底特律那些？ -但不是底特律原产
- From Detroit? - Yeah. Well, not originally, no.
救命，斯图回来了!
Help! Stuart's back!
管家怎么躺着了？
Why is the butler lying on his back?
他在装死
He's playing dead.
婆婆怎么躺着？
Why is Grandma lying on her back?
她死了
She is dead.
真是个怪节目
Oh, those wacky Sturgeons.
瞧，都死光光了
Look, they're all dead.
Thanks for watching [zeroxia@gmail.com] 2006.03.12